export const week1Items = [
  {
    id: 0,
    answer: "Program and Project Planning ",
    question:
      "provide the necessary process steps to scope out planning for systems",
  },
  {
    id: 1,
    answer: "Systems Design",
    question: "to analyze customer requirements",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    answer: "Software Requirements",
    question:
      "provide a systematic approach to development from multiple resources",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    answer: "Software Design / Development ",
    question: "systematic approach for the creation of software design",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    answer: "Software Implementation",
    question:
      "requirement for informal and formal integration testing, PROVIDE ASSURANCE that engineer builds function",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    answer: "Software Integration",
    question: "is processed through a configuration",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    answer: "Software and Systems Integration",
    question:
      "provides a consistent approach to effective integration activities",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    answer: "Software Subcontractor",
    question:
      "roles and responsibilities describe how a program and projects can benefit",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    answer: "Software and Systems Integration Delivery",
    question:
      "to provide assurance that both software and systems are integrated and working together",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    answer: "Product Evaluation",
    question:
      "provides the necessary process steps to conduct and perform continuous evaluations",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    answer: "Integration",
    question:
      "The act of bringing together smaller components into a single system that functions as one.",
  },
  {
    id: 11,
    answer: "Software",
    question:
      "A collection of instructions and data that tell a computer how to work.",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    answer: "System",
    question:
      "A group of interacting or interrelated elements that act according to a set of rules to form a unified whole",
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    answer: "System Architecture",
    question:
      "It is the conceptual model that defines the structure, behavior, and more views of a system.",
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    answer: "System Development",
    question:
      "It is the process of defining, designing, testing and implementing a new software application or program.",
  },
];

export const week2Items = [
  {
    id: 0,
    answer: "Program objectives ",
    question:
      "_______identify goals for the program with consideration of how these goals are to be accomplished.",
  },
  {
    id: 1,
    answer: "project managers",
    question:
      "At the senior management level, program and __________ are required to provide effective planning and focus so teams can be effective during software design/development activities.",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    answer: "Communication",
    question:
      "is a positive way for team members to understand your expectations.",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    answer: "Customers",
    question:
      "are best served by creating work products that can be used over a long period of time.",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    answer: "Project Plan",
    question:
      "The term “_________” is used throughout this process area to refer to the overall plan for controlling the project.",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    answer: "Project",
    question:
      "is any undertaking, carried out individually or collaboratively and possibly involving research or design that is carefully planned to achieve a particular aim.",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    answer: "Planning",
    question:
      "is the process of thinking about the activities required to achieve a desired goal. ",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    answer: "Computer program",
    question:
      "is a collection of instructions that can be executed by a computer to perform a specific task.",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    answer: "Teamwork",
    question:
      "It is an important element in all software programs and projects in order to achieve a common goal or to complete a task in the most effective and efficient way.",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    answer: "Team",
    question:
      "It is a group of individuals working together to achieve their goal.",
  },
];
